{
    "subject": "resource/Joyalukkas",
    "predicate": "ontology/regionServed",
    "object": "resource/Malaysia",
    "human_readable": "Joyalukkas operates in Malaysia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9814675450325012,
            "question": "Is Joyalukkas present in Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.957665741443634,
            "question": "Besides Malaysia, where else does Joyalukkas operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948865532875061,
            "question": "How long has Joyalukkas been operating in Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9294968843460083,
            "question": "What is the reputation of Joyalukkas in Malaysia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8523396849632263,
            "question": "Where does Joyalukkas operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.57700514793396,
            "question": "What kind of business is Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5588774085044861,
            "question": "What products or services does Joyalukkas offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49201732873916626,
            "question": "What are some of the popular products offered by Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4677024781703949,
            "question": "Is Joyalukkas a well-known brand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3962574601173401,
            "question": "Does Joyalukkas have any branches in other Asian countries?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joyalukkas operates in Malaysia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_874_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Joyalukkas a well-known brand?",
            "html": "dbpedia_874_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the popular products offered by Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_874_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products or services does Joyalukkas offer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_874_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_874_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Joyalukkas operates in Malaysia.\"\n\nHere's the evaluation based on the provided context information:\n\n* The documents mention that Joyalukkas has a presence in Singapore, London, UAE, Malaysia, Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, Kuwait, Qatar, Oman, and India. (Document 1)\n* Specifically, it is mentioned that Joyalukkas expanded its presence in Malaysia by opening its second showroom in Kuala Lumpur. (Document 2)\n* Additionally, the documents mention that Joyalukkas has a customer base of over 10 million customers worldwide and offers a wide range of jewelry at each of its showrooms, including in Malaysia. (Document 1)\n\nBased on this information, it can be concluded that Joyalukkas indeed operates in Malaysia.\n\nTherefore, the response is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support the statement \"Joyalukkas operates in Malaysia.\" For instance, multiple sources mention the opening and inauguration of Joyalukkas showrooms in Malaysia, including specific locations like LuLu Hypermarket, Capsquare Mall, Jalan Masjid India, and details about events such as the grand inauguration of its largest showroom celebrating a significant milestone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}